<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on 古文巡禮</title>
    <link>http://calmly5366.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on 古文巡禮</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This is a customized copyright.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:25:05 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://calmly5366.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>命學諸論</title>
      <link>http://calmly5366.github.io/posts/chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://calmly5366.github.io/posts/chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>欲識三元萬法宗，先觀帝載與神功。&#xA;坤元合德機緘通，五氣偏全論吉凶。&#xA;載天履地人為貴，順則吉兮凶則悖。&#xA;要與人間開聾瞆，順逆之機須理會。&#xA;理承氣行豈有常，進兮退兮宜抑揚。&#xA;配合干支仔細詳，定人禍福與災祥。&#xA;五陽皆陽丙為最，五陰皆陰癸為至。&#xA;五陽從氣不從勢，五陰從勢無情義。</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>滴天隨</title>
      <link>http://calmly5366.github.io/posts/chinese/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://calmly5366.github.io/posts/chinese/</guid>
      <description>甲木參天，脫胎要火，春不容金，秋不容土，火熾乘龍，水蕩騎虎，地潤天和，植立千古。&#xA;乙木雖柔，刲羊解牛，懷丁抱丙，跨鳳乘猴，虛濕之地，騎馬亦憂，藤蘿系甲，可春可秋。&#xA;丙火猛烈，欺霜侮雪，能煆庚金，從辛反怯，土眾生慈，水猖顯節，虎馬犬鄉，甲來成滅。&#xA;丁火柔中，內性昭融，抱乙而孝，合壬而忠，旺而不烈，衰而不窮，如有嫡母，可秋可冬。&#xA;戊土固重，既中且正，靜翕動辟，萬物司命，水潤物生，土燥物病，若在艮坤，怕沖宜靜。&#xA;己土卑濕，中正蓄藏，不愁木盛，不畏水狂，火少火晦，金多金光，若要物旺，宜助宜幫。&#xA;庚金帶殺，剛健為最，得水而清，得火而銳，土潤則生，土幹則脆，能贏甲兄，輸于乙妹。&#xA;辛金軟弱，溫潤而清，畏土之多，樂水之盈，能扶社稷，能救生靈，熱則喜母，寒則喜丁。&#xA;壬水通河，能泄金氣，剛中之德，周流不滯，通根透癸，沖天奔地，化則有情，從則相濟。&#xA;癸水至弱，達于天津，得龍而運，功化斯神，不愁火土，不論庚辛，合戊見火，化象斯真。</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Typography - Test for features</title>
      <link>http://calmly5366.github.io/posts/post-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 12:13:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://calmly5366.github.io/posts/post-5/</guid>
      <description>Lid est laborum et dolorum fuga. Et harum quidem rerum facilis est et expeditasi distinctio. Nam libero tempore, cum soluta nobis est eligendi optio cumque nihilse impedit quo minus id quod amets untra dolor amet sad. Sed ut perspser iciatis unde omnis iste natus error sit voluptatem accusantium doloremque laste. Dolores sadips ipsums sits.&#xA;Heading 1 Lid est laborum et dolorum fuga. Et harum quidem rerum facilis est et expeditasi distinctio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(No comment) When You Have Too Much to Do</title>
      <link>http://calmly5366.github.io/posts/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://calmly5366.github.io/posts/post-1/</guid>
      <description>You have a to-do list that scrolls on for days. You are managing multiple projects, getting lots of email and messages on different messaging systems, managing finances and personal health habits and so much more.&#xA;It all keeps piling up, and it can feel overwhelming.&#xA;How do you keep up with it all? How do you find focus and peace and get stuff accomplished when you have too much on your plate?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter I: The Grand Hall</title>
      <link>http://calmly5366.github.io/posts/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://calmly5366.github.io/posts/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Three hundred and forty-eight years, six months, and nineteen days ago to-day, the Parisians awoke to the sound of all the bells in the triple circuit of the city, the university, and the town ringing a full peal.&#xA;The sixth of January, 1482, is not, however, a day of which history has preserved the memory. There was nothing notable in the event which thus set the bells and the bourgeois of Paris in a ferment from early morning.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
